thehonestway.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement specifically applies to the way in which information is collected by this website, www.thehonestway.com. 

As the owner of this website, I respect your privacy and am committed to safeguarding your privacy whilst you are online here. 

The following paragraphs disclose how information is gathered and disseminated for this website. 

### RSS Feeds and Email Updates

If a user chooses to subscribe to RSS Feeds or Email Updates for this website, their contact information such as name and email address is requested. Users have the choice to opt-out of one or more of these communications at any time. Personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. This website operates a strict no-spam policy. 

### Log Files and Stats

This website uses log files gathered by Statcounter. Statcounter stores information including Internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, referring, exit and visited pages, date/time stamp, it tracks a user's movement within the website and gathers broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

### Cookies

This website does not use cookies. However, some advertisers that may appear from time to time on this website may use cookies for which I have no access to or control over. Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it's Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at [Google's Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

### Links

This website contains links to other websites. I am not responsible in any way for the privacy practices of these other sites. Users should be fully aware of this when they exit this website and to read the privacy statements of all websites that collect personally identifiable information that they visit. 

### Advertisers

External third party companies may display their advertisements from time to time on this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). These ads may contain cookies which I do not have access to or the information they collect. 

Please check the advertisers websites for their respective privacy policies.
